A Guide to the Zelma Wilson Architectural Collection, 1940-1995
Special Collections, Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University
Special Collections, Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University
Zelma Wilson Architectural Collection, 1940-1995 (Bulk 1969-1991)
Special Collections, Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University, Blacksburg, Va.
Ms1991-046
115.5 cu. ft. 24 record cartons; 177 rolled drawings; 5 map-case drawers
Wilson (1918-1996) an architect in Ojai, CA was born in New York City but later relocated to Southern California. She studied at the University of California, Berkeley, 1937-1940; later the California Institute of Technology, Pasadena, CA, 1941; and graduated with a B. Arch from University of Southern California in 1947. Wilson’s collection encompasses three decades of work that range from her academic through professional career—including her experience of operating her own firm. Her collection contains biographical material, professional committee and association work, school work, client correspondence, office promotional materials, time logs, drawings, photographs and manuscript material relating to projects. Materials range in date from 1940-1995 (bulk 1969-1991).
Wilson, Zelma, 1918-1996
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research.
Acquisition Information
The Zelma Wilson Architectural Collection was donated to Special Collections in 1991 with the bulk of the collection arriving in 1996.
Biographical Note
Wilson (1918-1996) was born in New York City but later relocated to Southern California. She studied at the University of California, Berkeley, 1937-1940; later the California Institute of Technology, Pasadena, CA, 1941; and graduated with a B. Arch from University of Southern California in 1947. Wilson was the only woman in her graduating class at USC that year. Her husband, a screenwriter, was blacklisted in 1952 after co-producing a film about New Mexico zinc miners. As a result the couple moved to Europe. While in Paris, Zelma pursued her post graduate studies at L’Ecole de Beaux Arts and her husband wrote "The Bridge on the River Kwai" and co-wrote "Lawrence of Arabia."
After working for the Los Angeles Planning Department, she obtained valuable experience in the offices of Richard Neutra, Victor Gruen Associates, R. M. Schindler, and Raphael Soriano. By 1957 Wilson was licensed and in 1967 she became principle of her own firm, Zelma Wilson and Associates, AIA, which she maintained continuously for over 20 years. She became a Fellow of the AIA in 1983 and guest lectured at Cal Poly San Luis Obispo for 10 years. As her practice grew Wilson acquired two partners and changed the firm name to Wilson and Conrad, Architects, AIA (1979-1984). The name shifted again as staffing and partnerships changed to The Ojai Group (1985-1986[?]) and finally Zelma Wilson, FAIA (1987[?]-1995).
Her projects started with houses and grew to institutional work, churches, and private schools. Wilson served on the California State Governors Emergency Task Force on Earthquake Preparedness from 1979 until 1985. Her projects include Vandenberg AFB Child Development Center, Ojai City Hall and the Simi Valley Community Center. Asked once by a prospective male employer if she cried on the job, Wilson answered, "I don't, but I've made a few contractors cry."
Scope and Content Note
Wilson's collection encompasses three decades of work that range from her academic through professional career—including her experience of operating her own firm initially Zelma Wilson and Associates and its many iterations (Wilson and Conrad Architects, The Ojai Group, and Zelma Wilson, FAIA). In the collection you will find biographical material, professional committee and association work, school work, client correspondence, office promotional materials, time logs, drawings, photographs and manuscript material relating to projects. Materials range in date from 1940-1995 (bulk 1969-1991) and are divided into three categories: Professional Papers, Office Records, and Project Records. Review the contents list below for details on individual categories.
Index Terms
Subjects:
Architectural drawing--20th century.; International Archive of Women in Architecture (IAWA); Women-owned architectural firms.
Genre and Form Terms:
Architectural drawings.
Occupations:
Architects.
Contents List
- SERIES I: Professional Papers, 1940-1993
  Scope and Content
  The Professional Papers series consists of material relating to Wilson's participation in professional life including licenses, correspondence, and involvement in professional and civic organizations. Wilson was involved with the California State Governors Emergency Task Force on Earthquake Preparedness (1979-1985), and the Ojai Beautiful Conference (1965-1975).
  - American Institute of Architects Fellow, congratulation letters, 1983 (Box-folder 22|1)
  - American Institute of Architects, National Convention Brochures, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 22|2)
  - California Council The American Institute of Architects, October 1977 (Box-folder 22|3)
  - California Council of Architectural Education, 1981-1983 (Box-folder 22|4)
  - California Polytechnic State University- Correspondence, 1974-1982 (Box-folder 22|5)
  - California Polytechnic State University, Lecture: Student Reports, 1979 (Box-folder 22|6)
  - California State Polytechnic, Pomona: Teaching Application, 1987 (Box-folder 22|7)
  - Carlos Diniz Associates, 1966 (Box-folder 22|8)
  - Colfax Property Sale, 1967-1971 (Box-folder 22|9)
  - Conferences and Exhibitions, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 22|10)
  - Correspondence, 1981-1983; 1988-1992 (Box-folder 22|11, Box-folder 22|12, Box-folder 22|13)
  - Credentials, 1940-1945 (Box-folder 22|14)
  - Earthquake Task Force: Earthquake Preparedness, 1981-1985 (Box-folder 22|15, Box-folder 22|17, Box-folder 22|18, Box-folder 22|16)
  - Historic Preservation Commission, 1991-1993 (Box-folder 22|19)
  - Left Handedness of Architects, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 22|20)
  - Licensing Examination Conference, 1988 (Box-folder 22|21)
  - Notes-Architect as Developer, n.d. (Box-folder 22|22)
  - Ojai Beautiful Conference, 1965-1975 (Box-folder 22|23, Box-folder 22|24, Box-folder 22|25)
  - Ojai Community Center Project Organizing Committee, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 22|26)
  - Ojai Planning/Architectural Commission, 1983 (Box-folder 22|27)
  - Open Space Committee: Ojai Valley, 1972 (Box-folder 22|28)
  - School work, California Polytechnic State University, 1983 (Box 63)
  - State of California: Board of Architectural Examiners, 1983 (Box-folder 22|29)
  - Union International Des Femmes Architects (UIFA) Conference, Seattle, WA, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 22|30)
  - Ventura County Chapter: American Institute of Architects, 1977-1979 (Box-folder 22|31)
  - Ventura County Chapter: American Institute of Architects: Awards Program, 1971-1979 (Box-folder 22|32)
  - Ventura County Chapter: American Institute of Architects – Design Award, 1988 (Box-folder 22|33)
  - Women in Architecture – Brochures and Articles, 1972-1982 (Box-folder 22|34)
  - Women in Architecture – Student Survey, n.d. (Box-folder 22|35)
  - Women in Architecture – West Coast Women’s Design Conference, 1974 (Box-folder 22|36)
  - Zelma Wilson - Biography/Resume (Box-folder 22|37)
  - Zelma Wilson - Miscellaneous Files concerning architecture, 1971-1983 (Box-folder 22|38)
  - Zelma Wilson-Profiles and Personal Statement, 1981-1991 (Box-folder 22|39)
- SERIES II: Office Records, 1967-1993
  The Office Records series consists of materials relating to the day-to-day operations of a private architectural practice including correspondence, office promotion materials, community involvements (Ojai Downtown Redevelopment, Ojai Valley Preforming Arts Theater), and proposals and promotions (1973-1993). It is divided into two series: General and Proposals.
  - SUBSERIES A: General, 1967-1992
    - Annexation of West Hills/Arbolada, City of Ojai, 1989 (Box-folder 23|1)
    - Book Keeping- Elaine Grove, 1987-1992 (Box-folder 23|2)
    - California State University, Qualified Architects List, 1984-1992 (Box-folder 23|3)
    - Consultants, various, 1984-1988 (Box-folder 23|4)
    - Correspondence and Miscellaneous sketches and notes, 1972-1975 (Box-folder 23|5)
    - Correspondence, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 23|6)
    - Correspondence, 1985-1988 (Box-folder 23|7)
    - Correspondence, 1990 (Box-folder 23|8)
    - Correspondence, The Ojai Group, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 23|9)
    - Cost Breakdown, 1975 (Box-folder 23|10)
    - Dron, Katherine, Invoices, 1975 (Box-folder 23|11)
    - Engineering Consultants, 1984 (Box-folder 23|12)
    - General specifications for drawings (Box 34)
    - GSA Form 254 – Completed, 1982-1991 (Box-folder 23|13)
    - GSA Form 254 – Completed, Wilson Firms and Others, 1982-1991 (Box-folder 23|14)
    - GSA Forms 255, 1980-1982 (Box-folder 23|15)
    - GSA Forms 255 for Projects - Completed, 1983-1986 (Box-folder 23|16)
    - GSA Forms 255 for Projects - Completed, 1983-1986 (Box-folder 23|17)
    - GSA Forms 255 for Projects, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 23|18)
    - Invitation to Office Opening Ceremony, 306 East Matilija, 1986 (Box-folder 23|19)
    - List of Blueprints in Storage, 1981-1989 (Box-folder 23|20)
    - Office Brochure, n.d. (Box-folder 23|21)
    - Office Faculty Study, 306 East Matilija, n.d. (Box-folder 23|22)
    - Office Promotion, 1974-1979 (Box-folder 23|23)
    - Ojai (City of), General Building and Construction Standards and Regulations (Box-folder 23|24)
    - Ojai Downtown Redevelopment Committee Reports, 1967-1972 (Box-folder 23|25)
    - The Ojai Group, Furniture Collection Drawings, 1985 (Box-folder 23|26)
    - Ojai Planning Commission, Architectural Review Brochure, 1981-1985 (Box-folder 23|27)
    - Ojai Valley Performing Arts Theater, 1989 (Box-folder 23|28)
    - Photographs: Foster A. Begg Immediate School (Box-folder 23|29)
    - Rainbow Valley Ranch, 1983 (Box-folder 23|30)
    - Renderings, miscellaneous projects, positives and negatives (Map-case 21|Drawer 5|Folders 42-43)
    - Ricketts, Barbara, Invoices for Graphics/Illustrations, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 23|31)
    - Roberson, Sea Ranch Design, 1968 (Box-folder 23|32)
    - San Buenaventura (City of) – Architectural Theme, 1972 (Box-folder 23|33)
    - St. Martha’s Episcopal Church Columbarium, West Covina, 1987-1989 (Box-folder 23|34)
    - Time log for various projects, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 23|35)
    - Time log for various projects, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 23|36)
    - Transparencies and Labels, n.d. (Box-folder 23|37)
    - Ventura (County of), Design Criteria and Specifications, Channel Islands Harbor, Shore side development, Aquatic development, 1980 (Box-folder 23|38)
    - Ventura County Chapter American Institute of Architects, Architectural Awards Program, 1977-1980 (Box-folder 23|39)
  - SUBSERIES B: Proposals, 1973-1993
    - Proposals, various, 1977-1980; 1991-1993 (Box-folder 24|1)
    - Agoura Hills, Postal Facility, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 24|2)
    - Atwater and Associates, Plaza Olivas Business Center, 1984 (Box-folder 24|3)
    - Baker/Dalrymple Residence Remodel, 1985 (Box-folder 24|4)
    - Brea-Olinda High School, Brea, 1985 (Box-folder 24|5)
    - Brooker, Furniture Repair Shop, 1985 (Box-folder 24|6)
    - Buena Park, Senior Citizen Center, 1981 (Box-folder 24|7)
    - Camarillo State Hospital, Children's Unit Improvements, 1986 (Box-folder 24|8)
    - Child Care Center Conversion, Los Angeles Air Force Station, 1982 (Box-folder 24|9)
    - Child Care Center, Fort Meade, Maryland, 1985 (Box-folder 24|10)
    - Child Care Center, Travis Air Force Base, 1991 (Box-folder 24|11)
    - Child Development Center, Fort Knox, Kentucky, 1985 (Box-folder 24|12)
    - Child Development Center, Fort Sheridan, Illinois, 1985 (Box-folder 24|13)
    - Child Development Centers, Republic of Panama, 1985 (Box-folder 24|14)
    - Child Development/ Religious Education Facility, Schofield Barracks, Hawaii, 1985 (Box-folder 24|15)
    - Chino Hills Development Plan, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 24|16)
    - Church of Epiphany, Westlake Village, 1988 (Box-folder 24|17)
    - Dalby Residence Addition, 1985 (Box-folder 24|18)
    - Ellsworth Residence, 1974 (Box-folder 24|19)
    - Florence Residence Garage Remodel, 1986 (Box-folder 24|20)
    - Happy Valley School, 1988 (Box-folder 24|21)
    - Harrison Residence, 1985 (Box-folder 24|22)
    - Kirkpatrick Residence, 1985 (Box-folder 24|23)
    - Lake Tahoe Community College Master Planning Application, 1985 (Box-folder 24|24)
    - Larch Avenue Elementary School, Los Angeles, CA (Dawie/Bretton/Wills Associates AIA, working in association with Wilson), 1985-1986 (Box-folder 24|25)
    - Macaluso Commercial Building, 1986 (Box-folder 24|26)
    - Manufacturing Tech Inc., New Facility Proposal, Ventura, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 24|27)
    - Marine Corps Air Stations Repairs, El Toro and Tustin, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 24|28)
    - Mount Cross Lutheran Church, Camarillo, 1985 (Box-folder 24|29)
    - Naval Construction Battalion Center, Applied Maintenance Facility: Plans and Specifications, Port Hueneme, CA, n.d. (Box-folder 24|30)
    - Naval Construction Battalion Center, Auto Maintenance Facility, Port Hueneme, CA, n.d. (Box-folder 24|31)
    - Naval Training Center, Applied Instruction Building, San Diego, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 24|32)
    - Noble Educational Foundation, Master Plan, 1985 (Box-folder 24|33)
    - Ojai City Hall, Services Wing remodel, 1991 (Box-folder 24|34)
    - Ojai Presbyterian Church, 1986 (Box-folder 24|35)
    - Oxnard, Redevelopment, City of Oxnard, 1982-84/Oxnard College, Occupational Education Building, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 24|36)
    - Oxnard Shores, 1974 (Box-folder 24|37)
    - Petit Residence, 1981 (Box-folder 24|38)
    - Philips Residence, 1987 (Box-folder 24|39)
    - Pugh, Dr. William, Medical, Dental, and Related Health Offices, 1989 (Box-folder 24|40)
    - San Buenaventura (City of), City Hall Annex Renovation, 1984 (Box-folder 24|41)
    - San Buenaventura (City of), Dudley Home Historic Park, 1977 (Box-folder 24|42)
    - San Buenaventura (City of), Police and Fire Headquarters, 1979 (Box-folder 24|43)
    - San Buenaventura (City of), Sanjon Maintenance Yard, 1981 (Box-folder 24|44)
    - San Simeon Visitor Center, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 24|45)
    - Santa Paula (City of), Civic Center & Boys and Girls Club, 1991 (Box-folder 24|46)
    - Simi Valley (City of), Interim Cultural Arts Center, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 24|47)
    - Southern California Edison Company, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 24|48)
    - St. Andrews United Methodist Church, 1985 (Box-folder 24|49)
    - St. Thomas Aquinas, 1989 (Box-folder 24|50)
    - Sykes Group, California Polytechnic Sports Recreational Facility, 1986 (Box-folder 24|51)
    - Thacher School, Library Addition – Correspondence, n.d. (Box-folder 24|52)
    - Tres Condados Girl Scout Council, 1973-1975 (Box-folder 24|53)
    - U.S. Postal facility, Camarillo, CA, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 24|54)
    - University of California San Diego, Day Care Center, 1989 (Box-folder 24|55)
    - University of California Santa Barbara, Residential Apartment Complex, 1989 (Box-folder 24|56)
    - University of California Santa Barbara, Administrative Services Building, 1989 (Box-folder 24|57)
    - Ventura (City of), Adult Recreation Center, 1978 (Box-folder 24|58)
    - Ventura (County of) Correctional Facilities, 1975 (Box-folder 24|60, Box-folder 24|59)
    - Ventura (County of), Design Development of Six County Parks, 1979 (Box-folder 24|61)
    - Ventura (County of), East Valley Sheriff’s Substation, 1981 (Box-folder 24|62)
    - Ventura County Historical Society, Agricultural Exhibit Building, 1983 (Box-folder 24|63)
    - Ventura (County of), Regional Park Report Project (Box-folder 24|64)
    - Ventura Professional Center, Phase II, 1975 (Box-folder 24|65)
    - Ventura Yacht Club, 1986 (Box-folder 24|66)
    - Youth Activity Center, Fort Riley, Kansas, 1985 (Box-folder 24|67)
- SERIES III: Project Records, 1956-1994 (Bulk 1969-1990) (Box 1-21, Oversize Map-case 25/Drawer 2, Oversize Map-case 21/Drawers 2-5, Box 25-218)
  The Project Records series contains drawings, photographs, correspondence, and other printed material relating to over 250 architectural projects carried out by Wilson and her firm.
  Arrangement
  The Project Records series has been arranged into a Project Index. which is a way to organize the various formats of architectural records from the same project. The index is arranged alphabetically by client name and contains information, where available, about the location, date, project type, architect, collaborators, and formats for each project in the collection.
  A Summary of the Project Index. is listed below. Consult the Project Index. for box numbers.
  Client Name/Project Title (location, date, architect/collaborator) [Format - Ms=Manuscripts, Dr=Drawings ]
  - Anderson, Don and Nita/ Whaley Anderson Residence Remodel (Ojai, CA,1975 Residence): [Ms,Dr]
  - Andrew Kwiat for Ray Consultants and Ojai Citrus Company/ Ojai Manor Hotel (Ojai, CA, 1980-1981 Commercial):[Ms]
  - Archibald, Tom and Dottie/ Archibald residence (Ojai, CA, 1973 Residence): [Ms, Dr]
  - Auric, Dr. Robert/ Ojala, private resort and seminar center ( Ojai, CA, 1980-1984 Commercial):[Ms,Dr]
  - Bank of America Bank of America, Ojai Branch (Ojai, CA, 1956 Commercial ):[Ms,Dr]
  - Bank of America Bank of America, Versateller Machine (Ojai, CA, 1987-1988 Commercial):[Ms,Dr]
  - Bard, Mrs. Thomas R./ Bard residence(n.d., Residence):[Ms,Dr]
  - Bendorf, Mr. and Mrs. /R.P. Bendorf residence(Ojai, CA, 1974-1975 Residence):[Ms,Dr]
  - Bertram, Mr. and Mrs. Ralph/ Bertram residence, remodel (Ojai, CA, 1968 Residence):[Ms]
  - Berwick, Keith and Sheena/ Berwick residence, remodel (Ojai,CA,1990 Residence):[Ms,Dr]
  - Billings Camera Colour Image Photography (Ojai,CA,1976 Commercial ):[Ms]
  - Bill's Bakery (Ojai, CA, n.d. Commercial):[Ms]
  - Bishop of the Protestant Episcopal Church in the Diocese of Los Angeles, a Corporation Sole/ St. Andrew's Episcopal Church (Ojai, CA, 1970-1973 Institutional):[Ms,Dr]
  - Blehm, Sue and Jack/ Blehm residence, remodel (Ojai, CA, 1986 Residence):[Ms, Dr]
  - Bloom, Andrea Tottenham/ Court at The Oaks (Ojai, CA, 1988 Commercial):[Ms]
  - Bordelon, Roxie and Dennis/ Bordelon residence, remodel (Camarillo, CQ, 1985 Residence):[Ms]
  - Boren, Mr. and Mrs./ Charles Boren residence, remodel (Ojai ,CA, 1976-1977 Residence):[Ms,Dr]
  - Bryan, Tom/ Senior Apartments (1984 Commercial/ Residence):[Ms]
  - Buckingham, Dr. Robert and Tracy/ Buckingham residence, remodel (Ojai, CA, 1987 Residence):[Ms, Dr]
  - Bulwa, Mr. and Mrs./ M.W. Bulwa residence(Ojai, CA, Residence):[Ms, Dr]
  - Burton, Cindy and Phil/ Burton residence (Ojai, CA,1989-1990 Residence):[Ms,Dr]
  - Caldwell, Robin (Ojai, CA,1990):[Ms]
  - California State University and Colleges/ California State Polytechnic University, Pomona, Student Housing (Pomona, CA, 1980 Institutional):[Ms, Dr]
  - California State San Bernardino/ Creative Arts Builidng (San Bernardino, CA,Institutional): Carl Maston, FAIA, architect:[Dr]
  - California State University, Los Angeles/ Child Development Center (Los Angeles, CA,1978-1986 Institutional):[Ms]
  - Chase, Mr. and Mrs. Donald/ Chase residence, remodel (Ojai ,CA, 1974-1975 Commercial):[Ms]
  - Churchill, Robert/ Churchill residence (Ojai,CA, 1980 Residence):[Ms, Dr]
  - Clark/ Clark residence (1985 Residence):[Ms]
  - Clark, Gillan/ Gillin's Massage studio(Ojai, CA,1977 Commercial):[Ms,Dr]
  - Cohen, Mitch/ Cohen residence (Ojai, CA, 1991 Residence):[ Ms]
  - College of Nations(1977 Institutional):[Ms]
  - Corey, Hope and Jeff/ Corey residence (Ojai, CA, 1986 Residence):[Ms, Dr]
  - Decuevas, Phyllis J./ Decuevas residence (Ojai, CA, 1978 Residence):[Ms]
  - Department of the Army Sacramento District, Corps of Engineers/ Vandenberg Air Force Base, Child Care Center(Santa Barbara Co., CA, 1982-1991Wilson and Conrad, Architects Institutional):[Ms, Dr]
  - Department of the Navy/ Southwest Division, Mess Hall (Port Hueneme, CA, 1967 Institutional):[Ms, Dr]
  - Di Giglio, Raymond J./ Di Giglio Duplex (Oxnard,CA, 1985 Residence):[Ms]
  - Dick Schaller in cooperation with the Optimist Club of Ojai/ Ojai Valley Civic Center (Ojai, CA, 1990 Commercial):[Ms]
  - Djanogly, Sidney/ project at Ojai Ave, Rincon, and El Paseo Streets (Ojai, CA, 1986 Commercial):[Ms]
  - Dreger, Mr. and Mrs. Robert/ Dreger residence (Ojai,CA,1979 Residence):[Ms]
  - Driskill, Mr. and Mrs. Bill/ Driskill residence (Ojai, CA, 1977-1978 Residence):[Ms, Dr]
  - Eaton, Commander Ralph/ Eaton residence (Ojai, CA,1977 Residence):[Ms]
  - Eaton, Major General and Mrs. Samaul/ Eaton residence, alterations (Ojai, CA, 1969 Residence):[Ms, Dr]
  - Edendale Terrace Tract - Residence, 2372 Loma Vista Place (Los Angeles, CA, Residence):[Ms]
  - Ellison, Mr. and Mrs. David/ Ellison residence (Ojai, CA,1972-1975 Residence):[Ms, Dr]
  - Evangelical Church Simi Valley/ Evangelical Church Simi Valley (Simi Valley, CA, 1984 Institutional):[Ms]
  - Fauvre, Dr. and Mrs./ Fauvre residence (Ojai ,CA,1975-1978 Residence):[Ms, Dr]
  - Fillmore, Dr. and Mrs. Paul/ Fillmore residence (Faria Beach, CA,1977 Residence):[Ms]
  - Finn, Pauline/ Finn Residence(Los Angeles, CA, 1977 Residence):[Ms]
  - First Baptist Church/ Muti-purpose building (Ojai, CA, 1976 Institutional):[Ms, Dr]
  - Fischer, Mr. and Mrs. Ames/ Fischer residence (Ojai, CA, 1980-1981 Residence):[Ms,Dr]
  - Fitzgerald, Ivon and Ruth/ Fitzgerald's Addition to Retail Space (Ojai, CA,1972 Commercial):[Ms, Dr]
  - Fitzgerald, Mr. and Mrs. Lee; Ruth Fitzgerald/ Fitzgerald Master Plan Subdivision (Meiners Oaks, CA,1978-1980 Residence):[Ms]
  - Florence, Jim/ Florence residence (Ojai,CA, 1988 Residence):[Ms]
  - Foggbank Group/ Foggbank Project [schematic drawings and studies for condominium units and group facilities in Marin Co.](Marin Co., CA, 1972-1973 Residence):[Ms,Dr]
  - Framson, Joel/ Dining room (Ojai, CA, 1977 Residence):[Ms]
  - Friend, G.E./ Friend's Ranch Remodel-Juicing Room (Ojai, CA, Commercial) :[Ms,Dr]
  - Frost, Kathy/Frost residence, remodel (Ojai ,CA,1989 Residence):[Ms]
  - Frost, Tim/Frost residence(Ojai, CA,1980 Residence):[Ms]
  - G.H. Palmer Associates/"La Dolce Vita" Apartments(Moorpark, CA, 1984 Residence):[Ms]
  - G.H. Palmer Associates/ Valencia Village condominium Projects(Newhall, CA,1984-1985 Residence): [Ms]
  - Ghitterman, Allan and Steve Schweitzer/ Ghitterman,Schweitzer, and Herreras a professional law corporation (Ventura, CA, 1977-1978 Commercial):[Ms,Dr]
  - Godfrey, Althea/Godfrey residence(Ojai,CA, 1987-1991Residence):[Ms]
  - Goldman, Michael and Giulia/ Goldman residence(Ojai, CA,1988 Residence):[Ms,Dr]
  - Goleta Union School Distict/ Study of portable building structures (Goleta, CA, 1984-1986 Institutional):[Ms]
  - Gould, Barbara and Richard/Gould Office Building (CA,1977 Commercial):[Ms, Dr]
  - Gould, Barbara and Richard/ Gould Residence- Remodeling of Bedroom /Remodel of Kitch/ Property Feasability (Ojai,CA, 1975 Residence):[Ms, Dr]
  - Graziano/Graziano's Pizza(Ojai, CA,Commercial):[Ms, Dr]
  - Graziano, Rose/Graziano's Beef Ranch Restaurant (Ojai, CA,1976-1977 Commercial):[Ms]
  - Greenberg, Bruce/Greenberg residence(Ojai ,CA,1973-1977 Residence):[Ms, Dr]
  - Grohe, Mr. and Dr./Grohe Residence Remodel (Ojai,CA,1985-1992 Residence):[Ms, Dr]
  - Hardyman/Hardyman residence(Los Angeles ,CA,1964 Residence):[Dr]
  - Hawkes and Associates/Lake Piru restroom facilities(Piru, CA,1984 Commercial):[Ms]
  - Hay, William/Pool house and Barbeque Shelter(Oak View, CA,1987-1988 Residence):[Ms]
  - Help of Ojai, Inc./Help of Ojai, "Little House," 111 Santa Anna St. (Ojai, CA, 1981-1986 Residence):[Ms, Dr]
  - Hercules Real Estate/Trash receptacle(Ventura,CA,1989 Commercial):[Ms]